Oleksii Mostovyi

e-mail: mostovoy.alexey@gmail.com

Mobile: 0410 256 252

LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/oleksii-mostovyi-b2159bb4</u> **Address:** 108 Sportsmans Drive, West Lakes SA, 5021

OBJECTIVE

Seeking a position where 5+ years of experience in software engineering and testing, and PC/Apple desktop support can be utilized and add value. I am an energetic team player, who promotes and supports a professional and efficient working environment.

With my outstanding customer service skills, a 'can-do' approach to all tasks, a willingness to develop new skills, and a consistently high level of communication and productivity, I believe I can be a valuable asset to any company who is searching for driven and motivated staff.

Oleksii Mostovyi 1 of 8

Soft skills:

- Passionate about quality
- Well organized
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Attentive to details
- Good operation and interaction with colleagues
- Work well in both team and autonomous environments
- Able to quickly respond to new challenges
- Willing and able to acquire new skills swiftly.
- Work well under tight deadlines and expectations.
- Able to recognise and prioritize workloads
- Willingness to share knowledge and experience, to benefit all.

Technical skills:

Hardware Knowledge and experience

- Diagnosed hardware faults and conflicts between peripherals.
- Installed and configured the following components:
 - Motherboards
 - CPU processors
 - o Ram modules
 - o Power supplies
 - Hard drives
 - o CD-ROM drives
 - Monitors
 - o Printers
 - Modem/Router/Firewall devices
 - USB/Firewire/Thunderbolt devices

Oleksii Mostovyi 2 of 8

Software Knowledge

- Identifying and resolving software conflicts
- Installed, configured and maintained the following software products:
 - o MacOS
 - Windows Desktop OS (all versions)
 - o Linux
 - Microsoft Office (all versions)
 - o Anti-Virus and Anti-Malware software
 - o 3rd Party applications from instructions

Software Engineering Knowledge

- Identifying, reporting and resolving software test environment conflicts
- Programming languages:
 - JavaScript
 - o Java
 - o Python
 - o SQL
- Experience working with the following:
 - Eclipse Integrated Development Environment (IDE)
 - o IntelliJ IDEA IDE
 - Version control systems: Git
 - Scrum Agile Software Developing Life Cycle (SDLC) Methodology
 - o PTC Integrity Lifecycle Manager
 - Jira Software Project incident management tool for Agile Teams
 - o Custom Plugins
 - Software Emulators
 - Application Programming Interface (API) and related libraries
 - Cloud based environments

Oleksii Mostovyi 3 of 8

WORK HISTORY:

Software Testing Automation Engineer

GlobalLogic, Lviv Ukraine

Sep 2015 – Jul 2017, and

Nov 2017 - Feb 2019

- System components and functions analysis
- Reviewing design inputs according to the scope of testing issues
- Creation and updating of UI and Functional Test Cases (manual and automation)
- Creation and updating the Traceability Matrixes
- Writing test cases for defect fix
- Automated test code-review and test stabilization
- Establishing automation testing environment
- Performing iteration analysis and test planning
- Selection and running tests for regression testing
- Reporting defects and monitoring their status until satisfactory resolutions have been implemented
- Performing fixes and build verification
- Change Requests analysis
- Functional testing:
 - Writing test scripts and test scenarios to meet acceptance criteria and quality standards
 - Documenting results of test executions including bug reporting
 - Performing formal testing to provide the results for the Federal Drug Administration (FDA)
 - Reviewing newly created/updated test designs, test cases and test scripts
- Management in sprint planning.
- Participation in knowledge-sharing activities

About company

GlobalLogic is a Digital Product Engineering Services company that was founded in 2000 and is headquartered in San Jose, California. GlobalLogic provides software product development services, including experience design, complex systems engineering, content engineering, and self-contained engineering labs. The company specializes in software engineering for cloud platforms, embedded software, Internet of Things, Automotive, mobile applications, and security.

About projects:

Software testing and reporting for the following:

- MiniMed™ 670G system with SmartGuard™ (automated medical insulin pump).
- Guardian™ Connect CGM (Continuous Glucose Monitoring) Mobile App.

Oleksii Mostovyi 4 of 8

Quality Assurance Testing Engineer

Rolique, Lviv Ukraine Jul 2017 – Nov 2017

- Analysing client requests for validity and feasibility
- Analysis of acceptance criteria to determine future development and testing activities for product concepts.
- Writing test scripts and test scenarios to meet acceptance criteria with strong focus on maintaining high quality standards
- Prepare assessment data to be used in product testing.
- Documenting results of test execution and bug reporting
- Participation in acceptance testing
- Creation and reviewing of product requirements, specifications and technical design documents
- Performing fixes and build verification
- Performing fortnightly demos for presentation to the product owners

About Company:

Rolique is a web development company, originally founded in Lviv, Ukraine. The company designs and develops mobile and web products for the businesses of EU (INTERMATE, IKEA etc).

About project:

CRM web application for the "INTERMATE Media GmbH" company. Provides a variety of useful tools for the managers of the company to create, schedule and update all events and activities associated with advertising campaigns for the company's customers.

Oleksii Mostovyi 5 of 8

Quality Assurance Test Engineer QA Light Training Center

Sep 2014 - Aug 2015

- Analyzed business requirements and suggested improvements to the product features
- Developed test cases for functional and regression testing of the project, Actify.
- Tested functional modules such as Home Page, Dashboard Page, Content Elements, Registration, My Profile, Friends, Places List, Activity, Messages
- Tested implementation of social networking features: blog, forum, instant messaging, new feeds
- Validated application's GUI for compliance with Usability guidelines published by US Department of Human Services
- Participated in cross-browser (MSIE, Firefox, Chrome, Safari) and cross-platform (Windows 8/7/XP, MAC OS X) testing in virtual machine (VMWare) environment
- Analyzed software failures, made them reproducible, reported bugs

About Company:

QA Light is a software development and IT training company, originally founded in Lviv, Ukraine. The company designs and develops mobile app and web products.

About project:

"Actify" - Social Event Discovery Platform – a web-based platform that delivers content and information on entertainment and business events within Europe.

Oleksii Mostovyi 6 of 8

EDUCATION/ TRAININGS/ CERTIFICATES

Additional education and training:

2015 - 2018, GlobalLogic training:

- Networking
- Linux
- Effective Project Management
- Bluetooth
- Agile SDLC Methodologies
- JavaScript (Advanced)
- Being Productive (A training course covering methods of developing appropriate work skills and using best practices on being productive autonomously as well as in teams)

2014, **QA Light Training Centre**:

- Networking
- Software Testing and Quality Assurance
- SQL (Structured Query Language)

Donetsk Music College

- Music Art
- Drumming
- Percussionist

LANGUAGES

- English IELTS score 6.5
- Ukrainian, Russian native speaker

Oleksii Mostovyi 7 of 8

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Hobbies and Interests

Music

- Drummer in several past bands
- Drum Teaching
- Learning to play:
 - Indian flute
 - o Piano
 - Guitar
- Sound engineering and video production

Vedic philosophy

- Study and practice 10+ years, the ancient tradition of Gaudiya Vaisnavism
- Bhakti Yoga participant
- Visited India on several occasions to deepen my knowledge of the ancient tradition of Gaudiya Vaisnavism

Psychology

- Researching different schools of psychology (biological, behavioral, cognitive, social)
- Attended several online personal development training courses

Sport

- Athletics
- Swimming
- Cycling

REFERENCES

- Oleksandr Bilyk Team Lead oleksandr.bilyk@globallogic.com
- Dmytro Porfirov Project Manager dmytro.porfirov@globallogic.com
- Aliona King President Slavia Ukrainian Cultural Center 0401 689 645
- Adrian Gravelle Teaching Technologist University of South Australia adrian.gravelle@unisa.edu.au 0434 549 598

Oleksii Mostovyi 8 of 8